Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Philosophy 32: "Models" Dan Gallin (Fall), 1966 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Handouts (Winter), 1973 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Burge's quantificational rules, undated (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Notes on Quine's methods (Third edition), 1972 August (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 32: Exams and answers (Winter), 1973 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 32: Records and final exams (Fall), 1971 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 32: Exams, answers, and distributions (Fall), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams (Fall), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 32: Student exams (Fall), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Student records (Fall), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Materials on alphabetic variance and proper substitution (Fall), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Language of Chapter IV (Fall), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Tautological implication, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 32: Class notes (Fall), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 32: Quiz 1, 1971 October (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32: Records and evaluations (Fall), 1971 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Examinations and answer sheet (Fall), 1977 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- "Argument Requiring Infinite Model: Invalidity in Identity" Gary Mar, ND. (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 133 (Spring), 1977 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 32: Description calculus, 1966-1979 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 32: Identity calculus notes useful for KM2, 1962-1966 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 31: Textbooks and references for first course in logic, 1965-1970 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Extra notes on 187B: Modal logic, principles of substitutivity (Spring), 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
- DuBois clubs correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Correspondence on the murder of Mrs. Barteaus' son (Guatemala), 1967 June 1 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Independent Action Association of Compton newsletter, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Indian Affairs newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Student Democratic Society newsletters, correspondence, and articles, 1967-1968 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Socialist Workers Party materials on election, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Yippies, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
- News articles and correspondence on Delano, 1967-1968 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Taxpayers Against the War correspondence, 1967 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Tax refund suits correrspondence, 1967 June, August (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Tax refund suit correspondence, 1967 August (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Tax refusal correspondence on Kalish vs. US, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Telephone tax brief by Mike Hannon, 1967 July 21 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Telephone tax memo from lawyer and correspondence with Altman, 1967-1969 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Papers and newsletter for WRL Tax Project LA Office, 1968 August (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Correspondence for ad hoc committee for statement on Czch/Viet, 1968 September 3 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- Ad hoc committee for cultural exchange with Russia, 1967 September 15 (Box 90, Folder 20)
- American Friends Service Committee correspondence and pamphlets, 1968 August 30 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- Amnesty International correspondence and newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Agenda for Committee for Awareness and Social Education (CASE) meeting, 1968 May 15 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- Committee of the Professions correspondence and newsletter, 1968 January (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Citizens for California Higher Education newsletter, undated (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Community Action Center San Pedro correspondence and newsletter, 1967-1968 (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Mailing list for tax refusal, 1967 April (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Southern California Taxpayers Against the War correspondence, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Correspondence on telephone tax case and Altman's bill, 1968-1969 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Telephone tax correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Telephone tax not paid newsletter (Quaker Action Group and Valley Unitarian Church), 1968-1971 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Tax claim forms, undated (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Southern California Tax Payers Against the War: Expenses and contributions records, 1967-1968 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Reverend Jones: Telephone tax correspondence, 1968 September 3 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Income tax (Spring), 1968 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  Correspondence on income tax for Ruth Kissane and Carl Mayfield.
- Handbook on non-payment of war tax, 1967 January (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- Correspondence with Kuchel and newsletter, 1967 May 29 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Correspondence regarding tax protest and acknowledgements, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Correspondence with Franklin Zahn (Tax Suit), 1971-1977 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Correspondence with IRS and Ambroz on tax refusal, 1968 September-December (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Correspondence with lawyers related to tax protest, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- IRS levies, 1971-1974 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Telephone bills and tax issue, 1972-1974 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Telephone bills and tax issue, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Recent levies by IRS, 1960-1970 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Correspondence for tax protest mailing list (Spring), 1967 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Correspondence with Taxpayers Against the War, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- VDC leaflets and announcements, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Publications on Vietnam from Glad Day Press, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Publications on radical education, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Publications, bibliographies, and reprint lists, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- CAW-SDS publications, 1968 November 25 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Publication on Vietnam, titled "Minority of One", 1968 August 15 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Publications and newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Peace Action calendar and newsletter, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Publications: Peace Press and Jerry Palmer, 1968 October (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Peace happenings and exchange leaflets, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Postal Instant Press newsletter, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- Sanity Now newsletter, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Vietnam Education Project correspondence and newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 17)
- Pierre Noyes (legality of war) correspondence and essays, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 18)
- Taxpayers Against the War and complaints about court rulings, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 19)
- Political literature, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 20)
- Vietnam protests newspaper clippings and correspondence, 1967 April (Box 92, Folder 21)
- Mobilization lecture and newsletter, 1967 April 15 (Box 92, Folder 22)
- Mobilization publicity and literature, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 23)
- Peace Movement history and questionnaire, 1965-1967 (Box 92, Folder 24)
- Regulations for campus organizations, 1966 July, September (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Newspaper article and Balcombe ad (Spring), 1967 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Bibliography selected by Kalish, undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Incidental literature on the war, 1967- 1968 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Information on Vietnam for a letter campaign, 1967 May 22 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- LA Times editorial and clippings on Vietnam, 1967 June (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Newspaper clippings and materials from peace groups, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Legality of the war books, pamphlets, and correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- National Lawyers Guild, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- National Emergency Civil Liberty Committee leaflets, undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Civil liberties, Steamler case against HUAC, 1966-1973 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- 20B notes and questions, circa 1950 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Textbook and materials for 20B (Fall), 1965 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 20B typed notes (Summer), 1954 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- 6B final, notes and details (Fall), 1963 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Anthology for Philosophy 6A, 1953 April 6 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 6A: Notes on knowledge and society, Plato, and moral economy, undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Material from Swarthmore, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
- History of Modern Philosophy 20B class assignments (Fall), 1949-1950 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 6A: Class assignments, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Lecture on Leibniz: "First truths, necessary and contingent truths, etc.", 1946 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Identity of indiscernibles, internality of relations essays, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
- Notes on Liebniz's lecture "The Problem of Innate Knowledge", undated (Box 94, Folder 8)
- Continental rationalism exam questions by Yost and Kalish, 1947-1954 (Box 94, Folder 9)
- Correspondence with Clarke on quantity of motion, 1955 January (Box 94, Folder 10)
- Swarthmore student papers on Descartes and Liebniz (Fall), 1946 (Box 94, Folder 11)
- Continental rationalism: Lectures on Descartes and Spinoza, and bibliography (Fall), 1954 (Box 94, Folder 12)
- Notes on Descartes and his predecessors, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Continental rationalism bibliography, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Notes on Spinoza, undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
- Papers by Benson Mates on Plato's Theory of Ideas, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
- Notes on Plato, and Mackay's seminar (Parmenides and Theaetetus), undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
- Plato and notes on different philosophy topics, undated (Box 95, Folder 6)
- Notes for the epistemology seminar; Broad, Morore, Stout, undated (Box 95, Folder 7-8)
- Contemporary philosophy, realism (Spring), 1950 (Box 95, Folder 9)
- Categories and interpretations notes, 1944 (Box 95, Folder 10)
- Book IV, metaphysics, notes on chapters 4-8, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
- Longhand notes metaphysics and physics, 1944 (Box 95, Folder 12)
- Notes related to Metaphysics Book 1, 1944 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  Dennes and Mackay's Lecture (anecdotal and academic).
- Contemporary philosophy notes and bibliography, 1955, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Contemporary philosophy notes and exam questions, 1950, 1955, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 15)
- Contemporary philosophy notes and lecture outlines (Spring), 1950 (Box 95, Folder 16)
- Contemporary philosophy notes and lecture (Spring), 1951 (Box 95, Folder 17)
- Contemporary philosophy notes and lecture (Spring), 1955 (Box 95, Folder 18)
- Contemporary philosophy notes from Philosophy 170A (Fall), 1958 (Box 95, Folder 19)
- Contemporary philosophy notes: British empiricism and Locke, 1950, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 20)
- Locke, bibliography and readings (Spring), 1956 (Box 95, Folder 21)
- Locke, undated (Box 95, Folder 22)
- Locke papers by Swarthmore class, 1946 November - 1947 April (Box 95, Folder 23)
- Lectures on Berkeley, British Empire, 1950, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- George Berkeley, notes on "Can Hylas conceive the unconceived.", 1957 November (Box 96, Folder 2)
- George Berkeley essay on vision, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
- George Berkeley notes, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
- George Berkeley lectures pertaining to dialogues, undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
- British empiricism, bibliography from George Berkeley, undated (Box 96, Folder 6)
- George Berkeley student papers, 1946 (Box 96, Folder 7)
- Notes on Hume, Moore's article, bluebook, and paper topics, undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
- Papers on Hume, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
- British empiricism final exam (Spring), 1956 (Box 96, Folder 10)
- Treatise: Notes Parts I and II, 1950 July 24, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  Final examination from 1956 enclosed.
- Treatise: Part III, 1950 July 27 (Box 96, Folder 12)
- Treatise: Notes, lectures Part IV, undated (Box 96, Folder 13)
- Treatise: Notes on Part IV, undated (Box 96, Folder 14)
- Hume's ethics paper, undated (Box 96, Folder 15)
- Bibliography for British empiricism, 1950-1955 (Box 96, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 170B: Lectures, bibliography, and exams (Spring), Spring 1959. (Box 96, Folder 17)
- Bibliography 170A, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 18)
- Contemporary philosophy, realism bibliography, lecture notes, and reference, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 19)
- Philosophy 170B (Spring), 1959 (Box 96, Folder 20)
- Philosophy 6B: Exams (Spring), 1952 (Box 96, Folder 21)
- Philosophy 6B: Rough draft of lecture (Fall), 1947 (Box 96, Folder 22)
- Philosophy 6B: Syllabus (Spring), 1952 (Box 96, Folder 23)
- Hume's dialogues, undated (Box 96, Folder 24)
- Philosophy 6B: Berkeley, Los Angeles (Fall), 1947-1948 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 6B: Bibliography, lectures, notes, and exams, 1952-1959 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 6B, 1947, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  Additional materials include a lecture by Kalish from 1947.
- Philosophy 6B: Weaver's scientist's beliefs, Ramsey epilogue, Hume's induction argument, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  Weaver's Scientist's beliefs, epilogue by Ramsey, Outline of Hume's argument on induction
- History of Greek philosophy (Winter), 1950 (Box 97, Folder 5)
- History of Greek philosophy (Spring), 1950 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Introduction to Philosophy 6B: Bibliography and pre-Socratic philosophy (Spring), 1950 (Box 97, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 20A: Exams and bibliography, 1964 January 24 (Box 97, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 6A: Readings in political philosophy (Spring), 1951 (Box 97, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 6A: Mill and Plato (Fall), 1947 (Box 97, Folder 10)
- Comments to Yost (Spring), 1951 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Material for 6A lectures on democracy and religion, 1951 April (Box 97, Folder 12)
- Outline of lectures, 1947 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Bibliographies, 1946-1948 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- History of Greek philosophy, pre-Socrates philosophy, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Kant, undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 20B: Final exam questions (Fall), 1965 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Correspondence on reviews, 1957, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- Review of introduction to semantics, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Review of Bierman's book (Fall), 1963 (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Tarski and logic articles, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Correspondence with church regarding reviews for JSL, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Review for frontier pamphlets and essays, 1958 April (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Referee job for UC president, 1970 April (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Referees report on Gentzen translations for UC press, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- George Cohen article, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Reviews of Leblanc and Slater, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Guides to reviewers for JSL, undated (Box 98, Folder 15)
- Review of Parry's article in JSL, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 16)
- Review of Beirman's manuscript, undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
- Review for Bierman's book, undated (Box 98, Folder 18)
- Review of Ambrose and Lazerowitz logic and theory of formal inference for JSL, 1961-1963 (Box 98, Folder 19)
- Review of Anderson and Johnstone deductive logic for Wadsworth Press, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 20)
- The Paper: Rough draft, undated (Box 98, Folder 21)
- The Paper: Manuscript, undated (Box 98, Folder 22)
- The Paper: Notes and outlines, undated (Box 98, Folder 23)
- Review for Massey and Canty for JSL, 1954-1965 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Charles Howard's set theory theorem, undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Mr. Graef, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
- A set problem suggested by Rolfe Eberle, undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Problem suggested by Mr. Van Zuyle, undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Equivalences among ordinals (Fall), 1961 (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Peano's Arithmetic with Zermelos def., undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
- "Definitions of Finiteness", essay by Vida Greenberg from Richard's Seminar at Berkeley, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Independence axiom of regularity, Richard's seminar at Berkeley (Spring), 1961 (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Translation of Frege-Monty Furth, undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 241: Extra copy of theorem list (Fall), 1958 (Box 99, Folder 11)
- Theorem list (Fall), 1961 (Box 99, Folder 12)
- A definition of ordinal number, J.R. Isbell, 1960 January (Box 99, Folder 13)
- Notes on set theory, natural numbers (Fall), 1956 (Box 99, Folder 14)
- Review of natural deduction, undated (Box 99, Folder 15)
- Review of natural deduction, 1964 November 10 (Box 99, Folder 16)
- Review of Introduction to Logic, undated (Box 99, Folder 17)
- Review of Introduction to Logic, 1964 February 29 (Box 99, Folder 18)
- Review of Introduction to Logic, undated (Box 99, Folder 19)
- Harper's Encyclopedia: Models in logic and science, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 20)
- Review of Natural Deduction, 1961 January 20 (Box 99, Folder 21)
- Letter to Faris, 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 22)
- "Review of Quantification Theory", 1965-1966 (Box 99, Folder 23)
- Suppes logic text, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 24)
- References on logic, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Magazine, journal, and correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 100, Folder 2)
- Chapter 8, Section 6+7 proofs and notes, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Chapter IX, Section 2, some proofs, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams with solutions, and materials from Chapter IX, 1962, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Chapter VIII proofs, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams with solutions, 1962, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 32: Records and course evaluations (Spring), 1978 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 32: Records and evaluations (Winter), 1976 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32: Records, student evaluations, handouts (Winter), 1973 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Spring), 1982 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 32: Final exam, student papers (Spring), 1982 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Winter), 1981 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 32: Final exams, student papers (Winter), 1981 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- Montague-Kalish proof, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- Montague-Kalish proof, natural deduction, 1967-1977 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 32: Final exam papers (Winter), 1985 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Final exam papers and notes from Wathan Salmon (Winter), 1985 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures and records (Fall), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures (Winter), 1987 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures (Winter), 1987 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Exam problems (Winter), 1976 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Exams (Winter), 1981 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 32: Exams, Dolinko (Winter), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 32: Exams (Fall), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32: Exams (Winter), 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32 (Spring), 1982 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 32: Kaplan exams (Winter), 1983 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 32: Possible exam questions, undated (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Lecture, exams, problems (Winter), 1984 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Records (Winter), 1980 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Faculty Association/American Association of University Professors correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 102, Folder 8-9)
- MAC examinations (Fall), 1971 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Masters qualifying exams (Fall), 1972 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Logic preliminary (Fall), 1970 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Logic (Spring), 1971 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Masters qualifying exam, 1969-1970 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Logic qualifying examinations (Fall), 1964 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Preliminary, exam, and questions (Spring), 1965 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Qualifying examinations: Logic (Fall), 1966 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Logic qualifying exam (Fall), 1966 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Logic qualifying exam (Spring), 1966 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Logic qualifying exam (Fall), 1968 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Logic qualifying exam (Fall), 1967 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Problem "extra" questions, 1964-1969 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Logic preliminary (Fall), 1962 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Logic qualifying exam (Spring), 1962 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Logic qualifying exam, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- MAC (Spring), 1975 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Qualifying and MA examinations, 1968-1969 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- MAC logic examination draft, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- MA logic examination and grades (Spring), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- MAC logic exam and results (Fall), 1973 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- MAC reports, logic (Spring), 1974 (Box 103, Folder 22)
- Assorted MA qualifying exams, 1963-1970 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- Philosophy Department qualifying exams, 1953-1967 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Logic MAC reports and papers (Spring), 1982 (Box 103, Folder 25)
- Philosophy 32: Tyler Burge, 1979-1980 (Box 103, Folder 26)
- Labelled "Evaluations by Church and Kalish. Note by Church. Ex. By Mar" (Winter), 1978 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- MAC: General report and logic exams (Spring), 1978 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- MAC: Logic (Spring), 1977 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Rough notes and Kalish's report (Spring), 1977 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Master comprehensive exams, 1977 April (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Part II of Carnap's copy, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Part II of first draft, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Translation from Le into Lm. Carnap, 1955 February 12 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Translation of Lm into Le. Carnap, 1955 February 11 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Definite descriptions and modalities, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Discussion with Carnap, 1955 February 5 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Notes by Carnap on quasi-intensions, 1955 February (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Kemeny-Carnap notes, 1954 June (Box 104, Folder 12)
- Discussion with Carnap and notes, 1954-1955 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Inductive logic, probability quiz, undated (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Discussion with Carnap and notes, 1954-1955 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Discussion with Carnap and notes, undated (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Carnap translation of Linto, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Part II Kalish's copy corrected, undated (Box 104, Folder 18)
- Part III Camup's copy, undated (Box 104, Folder 19)
- Carnap logic seminar, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 20)
- R. Carnap, Hilbert e-operator, undated (Box 104, Folder 21)
- Carnap notes on semantics, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 22)
- Carnap on aim of inductive logic, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- Carnap on theoretical concepts in science, 1960 February (Box 104, Folder 24)
- Bibliography and exam from semantics (Fall), 1953 (Box 104, Folder 25)
- Church: Reviews Cannap's semantics, undated (Box 104, Folder 26)
- Semantics, Korzybaki et al, 1948-1953 (Box 104, Folder 27)
- Definitions: Semantics, 1959-1960 (Box 104, Folder 28)
- Insignifica Semantica and correspondence, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Reichenbach on nomological statement, 1948-1950 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Liar paradox (Spring), 1957 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Semantics (Fall), 1951 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Paradoxes, Tarski and others, undated (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Semantics materials, bibliographies, quizzes, and proofs, 1951-1955 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Notes from semantics courses (Fall), 1950 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Count Korzybski on "The Barber", 1948 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Book, outline, and notes on linguistic expression and semantics, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Notes on Goddman's literature, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
- General of the material oriterion, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Notes on "Meaning and Necessity" and R. Carnap, 1946 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Quine: Existence and necessity, 1939-1943 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 240 (Fall), 1957 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 240 (Fall), 1956 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 240 (Fall), 1956 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 240, undated (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Definition for value and satisfaction, undated (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Philosophy 240 (Fall), 1956 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 240 (Fall), 1956 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Validity of axioms of descriptions, undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 240 rough notes on value and satisfaction (Fall), 1956 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Iotaless terms, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 240: Recursive definition of value and satisfaction for terms and formulas (Fall), 1956 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 240: Completeness argument (Fall), 1956 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Theoretischen logic, Hilbert-Ackermann, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)